

**AMRIZ JANTAN** Junior Full Stack Developer

### **ABOUT ME**

Certified Full Stack Developer with analytical and creative skills in addition to strong entrepreneurship. Multidisciplinary background with 7+ years experience in business modelling, branding and management that include both physical and digital operations as Co-founder of a Japanese lifestyle store. 9 years of experience in the corporate environment as a Senior Risk Analyst, responsible for complex risk assessments and key corporate clients' advisory.Portfolio: amrizjantan.github.io/Portfolio-RevampLInkedin:@a

N. Sembilan, Malaysia

amrizjantan@googlemail.com

+49 017632282463

Beckstraße 2 Hamburg, Germany

## **LANGUAGES**

Bahasa Malaysia: Native

English: Expert

German: Advanced

Japanese: Intermediate

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2021 - present

## JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER Freelance

Hamburg and Berlin, Germany

- Jointly responsible for developing a fully responsive webshop, both design and technical requirements www.bluesleeve.de using Wordpress technology.
- Webshop maintenance.

#### November 2014 - present

CO-OWNER

Bluesleeve www.bluesleeve.de

Hamburg, Germany

- Assumed full responsibility in overseeing all aspects of business with focus on business development and create conceptual business module, plans and goals to ensure maximum profits with minimal risk.
- Oversee daily operations of retail store and online.
- Collaborate with artists and designers on art exhibitions and business projects.
- Responsible business tax preparation, bookkeeping, payroll and general accounting.

### January 2008 - October 2013

**RISK ANALYST** 

Hamburg, Germany

- Risk assessment and advisory for diverse financial services and public listed multinational companies emphasizing on political, financial and management risks as well as crisis management framework.

### **EDUCATION**

2022

**FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM** Career Foundry, Web Development

Berlin, Germany

2002

**BACHELOR'S DEGREE** MARA University of Technology, Risk Management

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

# **SKILLS**

